defcad.org 2018-09-23

# Privacy | DEFCAD

**Defense Distributed Privacy Policy**  
Last Modified: 8/25/2017 

**1\. Introduction.** Defense Distributed ("Company" or "We") respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy. This policy describes the types of information we may collect from you or that you may provide when you visit the website www.defdist.org (our "Website") and our practices for collecting, using, maintaining, protecting, and disclosing that information. 

This policy applies to information we collect: 

  * On this Website. 
  * In email, text, and other electronic messages between you and this Website. 
  * Through mobile and desktop applications you download from this Website, which provide dedicated non-browser-based interaction between you and this Website. 
  * When you interact with our advertising and applications on third-party websites and services, if those applications or advertising include links to this policy. 

It does not apply to information collected by: 

  * any third party, including through any application or content (including advertising) that may link to or be accessible from the Website. 

Please read this policy carefully to understand our policies and practices regarding your information and how we will treat it. If you do not agree with our policies and practices, your choice is not to use our Website. By accessing or using this Website, you agree to this privacy policy. This policy may change from time to time. Your continued use of this Website after we make changes is deemed to be acceptance of those changes, so please check the policy periodically for updates. 

**2\. Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It.** We collect several types of information from and about users of our Website, including information: 

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline ("personal information"); 
  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and 
  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details. 

We collect this information: 

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us. 
  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. 
  * From third parties, for example, our business partners. 

**3\. Information You Provide to Us.** The information we collect on or through our Website may include: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Website. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Website, subscribing to our emails, including newsletters and updates, posting material, or submitting requests. We may also ask you for information when you report a problem with our Website. 
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us. 
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Website and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before placing an order through our Website. 
  * Your search queries on the Website. 

**4\. Information We Collect Through Automatic Data Collection Technologies.** As you navigate through and interact with our Website, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including: 

  * Details of your visits to our Website and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Website. 
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type. 

The information we collect automatically is statistical data and does not include personal information, but we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to: 

  * Estimate our audience size and usage patterns. Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Website according to your individual interests. Speed up your searches. Recognize you when you return to our Website. 

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include: 

  * Cookies (or browser cookies). A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Website. 
  * Flash Cookies. Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Website. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies. 
  * Web Beacons. Pages of the Website and our e-mails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).
